Guide to the General Frederick Steele Papers, 1845-1965 (inclusive), 1862-1868 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- Series II. Katherine B. Steele Papers
  - Miscellaneous printed material
    - Magazines and Clippings - Current oversize, placed on top of box (Box 18, Folder 59)
Olvera, Rafael. 5-67-2.
114th Regiment Ohio Infantry Volunteers. 4-44-36.
161st Regiment New York Volunteers. 3-37-17.
O'Neal, A. W. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Oppenheimer, J. 6-83-12, 13, 14 (copy).
Ord, Edward Otho Cresap. (1818-1883). 2-20-3 (m.); 3-42-20 (m.).
Ordnance, Chief of Artillery and SEE Division of West Mississippi-Chief of Artillery and Ordnance.
Oregon. 6-73-3, 11; 76-16 6-80-6; 6-85-8; 6-76-14. [SEE ALSO: Cities].
Oregon Volunteers. 6-73-1 (m.).
O'Reilly, Thomas. 2-27-4.
Orff, Henry. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Osterhaus, Peter Joseph. (1823-1917). 4-50-[9-11 (copies)], 12, 13 (copy), 24 (tel.); 4-51-38, [41-42 (tels.)], [69-70 (tels.)], [88-90 (tels.)]; 4-52-26 (copy), 33; 4-53-18 (copy), 19, 28 (tel.); 5-55-26; 5-56-24 (tel.); 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Owen, Timothy. 3-38-9 (by clerk); 4-45-25; 4-46-26.
Pacification Policies. 1-9-2, 3, 16, 18, 22; 1-10-22, 30; 1-11-34; 2-16-8.
Paddock, Joseph Williamson. 1-3-12 (copy); 1-5-10.
Palmer, M. L. 6-88-10.
Palmer, Sarah. 2-23-12.
Park, T. W. 1-1-4; 1-3-5.
Parker, Amasa Junius (1807-1890). 3-35-17.
Parker, Anna F. 1-1-3, 15.
Parsons, E. B. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Parsons, Lewis Baldwin (1818-1907). 2-23-15.
Paulina (Piute Indian). 6-73-8 (m.).
Peabody, O. 3-37-40.
Peck, D. B. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Peck, John James (1821-1878). 2-26-28 (printed).
Peirce, S. S. 2-14-2.
Pennington, Alexander Cummings McWhorter (1810-1867). 6-78-4.
Pensacola, Florida. 4-44-20; 4-45-10; 4-46-[30-33], 53; 4-47-33, 34; 7 (vol.)-(m.); 8 (vol.)-([UNK]
Pensacola, Florida-Maps. 4-49a-[1-5]. [SEE ALSO: Blakely, Alabama; Mobile, Alabama; Spanish Fort, Alabama].
Pensacola Department, Fort Pickens, Florida. 4-45-26.
Pent, Samuel. 4-53-29.
Perry, Alexander James. 6-73-4 (stamp).
Perry, Raymond H. 5-65-3.
Peters, George B. 1-8-12a.
Petersburg, Virginia. 4-52-3.
Phelps, John Smith (1814-1886). 2-30-18; 3-33-34.
Pickard, A. J. 4-46-28.
Pickering, William (Governor of Washington). 6-72-15; 6-76-2.
Pike, Mrs. Albert. 6-88-11.
Pile, William Anderson (1829-1889). 4-51-9; 5-55-15; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Pilot Knob, Missouri. 2-28-13.
Pine Bluff, Arkansas. 1-10-8; 2-27-25; 2-28-9; 6-71-5.
Pitzman, Jul[iu]s. 1-4-6, 12.
Piute Indians. 6-73-8.
Pleasant Hill, Louisiana, Battle of 1-12-8.
Pohlers, A. 1-4-7.
Point Reyes, California. SEE Punta de los Reyes Ranch.
Pollard, William S. 4-47-29; 5-66-20; 5-67-21; 6-68-10.
Pollard, Alabama. 4-49-26; 7 (vol.)-(m.); 8 (vol.)-(m.).
Pontonier Corps. 4-46-25.
Pope, Hamilton. 2-15-33.
Pope, John (1822-1891). 1-2-1, 2.
Port Townsend, Washington. 6-72-11.
Porter, George H. 4-51-21.
Porter, Henry M. 5-64-21, 22.
Portland, Oregon. 6-75-2, 3, 8; 6-78-6; 6-86-10.
Potter, O. O. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Prado, Apolinaria. 5-67-6, 7.
Prentice, George D. 2-15-33.
Price, O. F. 3-34-36.
Proctor, Emma H. 6-87-2b (copy).
Proctor, Thomas E. 6-87-5, 6.
Proctor, Mrs. Thomas E. 6-87-5, 6.
Provost Marshall General SEE Department of Arkansas-Provost Marshall General.
Puget Sound, Washington. 6-72-11, 15; 6-73-11.
Pugh, Henry L. 5-64-23, 24.
Punta de los Reyes Ranch (Point Reyes, California). 1-1-4; 1-3-5.
[Purington], D. V. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Putnam, Henry R. (d. 1872). 4-44-20.
Quartermaster General's Office, Washington, D. C. 6-73-4; 6-75-12.
Quartermaster General's Office-Property Division. 6-75-5.
Raleigh, North Carolina SEE Division of Mississippi.
Ramsay, George Douglas (1802-1882). 2-26-3 (m.).
Ready, E. S. 5-57-35; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Rebel Archives. 5-62-33.
Red River [Arkansas] Campaign (Southwest Arkansas Campaign). 1-12-8; 1-13-2.8, 11-20; 2-14-[2-4], 6,[8-11]; 2-15-2, 3, 6.
Reed, Samuel A. 4-47-27; 4-49-32b.
El Republicano. 6-71-11, 12.
Reserve Corps, Military Division of West Mississippi. 3-36-6, 9; 3-37-4, [14-16], 26, 27; 7 (vol.). [SEE ALSO: 1st Grigade Reserve Corps; 4th Brigade, 1st Division, Reserve Corps; 3rd Brigade, Reserve Corps; 3rd Brigade, 1st Division, Reserve Corps.
Rew, Bradford B. 4-51-91 (copy).
Reynolds, Joseph Jones (1822-1899). 2-21-2 (m.); 2-29-11 (m.), 17; 2-30-8 (m.), 19, 21; 3-32-19 (m.); 3-33-27.
Rhoades, Lawrence. 4-49-21; 4-54-11; 5-55-8; 5-57-4, 36; 5-58-1; 5-64-17 (m.).
Rhodes, Hinman. 5-64-26; 6-71-26.
Rice, Charles S. 3-41-8; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Rice Samuel Allen (1828-1864). 2-14-8; [6-88-12].
Richmond, Virginia. 4-52-3.
Rike, William H. H. 5-65-9, 10; 5-66-11; 5-67-16, 17; 6-68-6.
Rio Bravo, Texas. 5-64-1, 2.
Rio Grande, Texas. 5-59-16; 5-60-1; 5-61-8; 5-62-15; 7 (vol.)-(m.).
Ritter, Richard. 3-40-9; 4-43-20, 21; 7 (vol)-recipient.
Robbins, J. R. 6-83-13, 14 (copy).
Robles, Luis. 5-63-7, 8, 10 (m.); 6-68-13.
Rochester, Montgomery. 1-12-2; 2-30-20 (stamp), 29 (stamp).
Rockwood, Shepard S. 3-41-44; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Rodriguez, Gonzales. 5-67-6, 7.
Rogers, Anthony Astley Cooper (1819-1899). 2-16-8.
Rosecrans, William Starke (1819-1898). 2-28-13; 2-31-19.
Rouse, J. D. 5-62-44; 7 (vol.).
Rousseau, Lovell Harrison (1818-1869). 6-79-12 (m.); 6-80-2 (m.); 6-87-1 (m.).
Rowse, Albert. 3-36-30; 3-37-7; 3-40-24, 33; 4-43-30; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Royston, Y. L. 5-55-21 (copy).
Rucker, Daniel Henry (1812-1910). 6-81-7.
Ruggles, George David. 1-1-2.
Rush, J. B. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Russell, _____. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Russell, Edwin. 6-75-10.
Sachs, Henry. 3-32-16, 17; 3-35-23.
Sagendorph, M. 4-49-5.
St. Louis, Missouri. SEE Department of the West.
Salomon, Charles Eberhard. 1-13-17; 2-14-5.
Salomon, Frederick (1826-1897). 2-15-2, 12.
Sample, James Blaine (d. 1868). 4-49-22.
San Juan Island, Washington. 6-72-11; 6-82-3.
San Luis Obispo [California] Ranch. 6-74-2, 5, 8.
San Roman, Jose. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Sargent, Charles Sprague (1841-1927). 3-38-3.
Sawtelle, Charles Greene. 3-36-35; 3-41-28, 29, 45; 4-51-10; 4-54-12 (tel.); 6-73-2.
Sawyer, Roswell Miner. 1-11-38.
Scammon, Charles Telfant. 1-3-2 (m.); 2-28-[17-19]; 3-35-2; 3-42-46 (m.); 7 (vol.).
Scammon, J. Young. 2-24-3.
Schofield, George Wheeler (d. 1882). 6-80-2.
Schofield, John McAllister (1831-1906). 1-8-6; 1-9-19.
Scott, Caroline L. 2-19-6; [2-30-26?].
Scott (Miss) J. 1-11-26.
Scott, J. E. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Scott, Robert Nicholson (d. 1887). 6-72-11, 13; 6-74-7; 6-75-1, 6 (copy), 14 (copy); 6-80-8 (copy); 6-82-7 (copy).
Sears, Francis A. 4-47-29.
Seawell, C. G. 3-39-18.
Seawell, Thomas D. 2-24-10.
2nd Battalion Nebraska Cavalry. 2-18-27.
2nd Battery Massachusetts Light Artillery. 3-40-34 4-43-27.
2nd Brigade, 1st Division (Reserve Corps), Military Division of West Mississippi. 3-41-19 (m.) 4-43-10 4-44-5, 20b [SEE ALSO: Reserve Corps].
2nd Connecticut Light Battery. 6-71-21; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
2nd Division, 7th Army Corps. 2-31-24.
2nd Division, 16th Army Corps. 4-49-22.
2nd Division, 13th Army Corps. 4-45-27; 4-46-4, 27; 4-48-5; 4-49-23, 33; 4-52-7; 4-54-13; 5-55-27, 28; 5-58-15.
2nd Illinois Cavalry-Detachment. 4-47-15.
2nd Regiment Maine Veteran Volunteer Cavalry. 3-36-20; 4-46-28.
2nd Veteran New York Cavalry Volunteers. 4-47-48.
Selma, Alabama. 5-57-1; 7 (vol.)-(m.).
Separate Cavalry Brigade-Barrancas, Florida. 4-47-49; 4-48-4, 15; 4-49-[24-27].
17th Ohio Battery. 3-41-8.
7th Army Corps. 1-9-23; 1-11-36, 37; 1-13-[3-5]; 3-60-11. [SEE ALSO: 1st Brigade, 3rd Division; 2nd Division; 3rd Brigade, 3rd Division; 3rd Division].
7th Massachusetts Battery Light Artillery. 5-65-12; 5-66-17; 5-67-3, 4; 6-71-22; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
7th Vermont Veteran Volunteers. 5-64-21, 22; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
77th Chio Volunteer Infantry. 5-64-23, 24.
76th U. S. Colored Infantry. 4-46-5.
Shafter, James McM. 1-1-4; 1-3-5.
Shafter, Oscar L. 1-1-4; 1-3-5.
Shearer, Sextus H. 6-71-19a, 19b.
[Shearman], W. P. 6-80-5.
Sheetz, Josiah A. (d. 1883). 3-36-40.
[Sheldon], Edwin [U.]. 1-3-2.
Sheldon, William C. 1-12-20.
Sheridan, Philip Henry (1831-1888). 2-22-13 (m.); 2-27-2 (m.), 23 (m.); 2-31-31 (m.); 4-51-20 (copy); 5-59-6 (m.), 16 (m.); 5-60-4; 5-61-8, 17 (copy), 30, 31; 5-62-6 (copy), 10, 15, 38; 5-63-9; 5-64-10, 11; 5-67-8 (copy); 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Sherman, William Tecumseh (1820-1891). 1-3-10; 1-4-15; 1-7-4 (m.); 1-11-6, 22 (m.), 29 (tel.); 2-25-7 (m.); 3-32-7 (m.); 3-35-11 (copy); 4-51-47; 4-54-21 (copy).
[Shoch], W. H. 3-41-43.
Shreveport, Louisiana. 1-11-6.
Sickles, Daniel Edgar (1819-1914). 1-10-16 (m.), 18 (m.), 29 (m.); 3-34-11.
Siegendoff, U. 8 (vol.)-recipient.
Signal Officer, Chief SEE Department of the Gulf.
Simpson, D. S. 4-51-43.
16th Army Corps. 4-51-22; 5-55-3; 5-57-5, 41; 5-62-28. [SEE ALSO: 2nd Division, 16th Army Corps].
6th District, New Orleans, Louisiana. 5-55-8.
69th Battalion Indiana Infantry Volunteers. 4-45-12.
Slack, James Richard (1818-1881). 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Slaughter, James E. (d. 1901). 5-67-8 (m.).
Slavery. 1-2-3; 1-3-12; 1-4-2/ 3; 1-9-8.
Smith, Andrew Jackson (1815-1897). [1-4-16]; 7 (vol.)-recipient; 8 (vol.)-recipient.
Smith, Arden R. 5-59-12.
Smith, Mrs. Edmund Kirby. 1-10-38, 39.
Smith, Giles Alexander (1829-1876). 6-69-3 (copy); 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Smith, Joseph Rowe (d. 1868). 1-10-23; 2-31-13; 4-51-23; 5-60-11.
Smith, Camp C. F., Oregon SEE Camp C. F. Smith, Oregon.
Sneath, R. G. 1-9-7b (copy).
Snow, Josiah. 1-9-11, 13.
Snow, William D. 1-9-29; 6-71-5.
Sokalski, George Oscar (d. 1867). 1-8-11; 2-27-24; 3-35-26.
Soper, R. R. 3-41-40, 41.
Southern Division of Louisiana. 4-43-28, 31; 4-44-6.
Southwest Arkansas Campaign. SEE Red River [Arkansas] Campaign.
Southwick, H. K. 4-45-13.
Spanish Fort, Alabama. 4-48-21; 4-51-6, 61, 67, 78; 4-52-19, 20; 5-55-33; 7 (vol.)-(m.); 8 (vol.)-(m.).
Spanish Fort, Alabama-Maps. 5-56-1, [3-5]. [SEEAALSO: Blakely, Alabama; Mobile, Alabama; Pensacola, Florida].
Speed, Frederic. 3-40-21, 29; 3-41-2; 3-42-2, 22, 34, 48; 4-43-18, 28, 31; 4-44-6.
Speed, James. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Spicely William Thomas (d. 1884). 4-45-31, 32; 4-47-2, 29; 5-55-14, 18.
[Sproule], G. [W.]. 1-3-1, 3.
Spurling, Andrew Barclay. 4-48-6, 27 (copy); 4-49-8; 4-51-43, [44-46], 71 (tel.), 87; 7 (vol.)-recipient; 8 (vol.)-recipient.
Stanton, Edwin McMasters (1814-1869). 1-4-8b (copy); 1-6-5 (stamp?); 5-61-27a (copy); 6-74-3.
Starkloff, H. M. 6-88-13a.
Steele, A. E. (Mrs. John B.?). 3-33-4.
Steele, E. B. 5-67-10.
Steele, Edgar W. 1-1-4; 6-88-13b.
Steele, Ella. 1-7-1b (copy). [SEE ALSO: Brooks, Ella Steele].
Steele, George. 1-1-4; 1-3-5; 6-70-1a; 6-74-2, 13.
Steele, Isaac C. 1-1-4; 1-3-5; 6-74-8.
Steele, John Benedict (1814-1866). 1-2-3 (printed; 1-9-8, 14, 20; 1-10-16, 18; 2-15-7; 2-27-15; 3-33-2, 6; 6-69-9; 6-72-12, 14; 6-74-13 (m.); 6-86-16 (m.).
Steele, M. N. 1-1-1a.
Steele, Rensselaer E. 1-1-4; 1-3-5.
Steele, Camp, Washington SEE Camp Steele, Washington.
Stepp, G. W. 4-46-26 (copy).
Stevens, Hazard. 6-74-9 (m.).
Stevens, William E. 5-60-2; 5-64-23, 24.
Stewart, James M. 4-47-46.
Stillman, George L. 4-52-38; 4-53-52; 4-54-6, 7.
Stoneman, George (1822-1894). 6-73-7.
Storer, Newman Wu 3-37-41; 5-55-11; 5-65-12; 5-66-17; 5-67-3, 4; 6-71-22; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Strong, D. 6-72-2b (tel.).
Strong, Richard Polk (d. 1903). 5-55-34; 6-73-8; 6-74-14; 6-75-2, 6, 8, 13, 14; 6-77-4, 6; 6-78-1; 6-80-7, 8, 11; 6-81-[2-5]; 6-82-2, 5, 7, 8, 9; 6-83-4, 6, [8-11], 14; 6-34-2, 3, [6-8], [10-15]; 6-85-[2-4], 6, 8, 10, 11; 6-86-4, 6, 8; 6-87-1.
Subsistence, Commissaries of SEE Board of Examiners of Commissaries of Subsistence.
Suffolk-Chancelloraville, Virginia; Siege of 2-26-28. [SEEALSO: Chancellorsville, Virginia]
Sullivan, Peter John (d. 1883). 2-14-14, 15; 2-29-33.
Surgeon, Senior SEE 4th Brigade Reserve Corps Military Division of West Mississippi-Senior Surgeon.
Surratt, Isaac. 6-68-8 (m.), 15 (m.), 16 (m.).
Swan, L. W. 4-53-56.
Tamaulipas, Mexico. 5-63-21, 22.
Tassara. 6-71-8 (m.).
Taylor, George W. 3-36-31; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Taylor, James M. 5-65-14.
Teal, Joseph. 6-83-5, 6; 6-84-9; 6-86-5, 6(copy).
Tendick, Robert P. 3-42-56.
Terrill, Mrs. George. 1-1-1.
Texas. 1-10-46 (map); 5-61-13; 7 (vol.)-(m.). [SEE ALSO: District of Texas].
Thatcher, Horace Kellogg (d. 1877). 4-51-47.
Thayer, John Milton (1820-1906). 1-4-4; 1-10-45; 2-14-9; 2-18-25, 26; 2-28-14.
Thayer, Royal H. (notary). 1-1-4.
3rd Brigade, 1st Division, Reserve Corps. 3-42-28, 57; 4-43-32; 4-44-14, 30.
3rd Brigade Reserve Corps. 3-36-7, 10, 21; 3-38-2, 40; 3-40-18; 3-41-20 (m.); 4-43-38; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
3rd Brigade, Reserve Corps, Military Division of West Mississippi-Detachment. 3-40-41.
3rd Brigade, 3rd Division, 7th Army Corps. 1-13-8.
3rd Division, 7th Army Corps. 1-11-36, 37; 1-13-[[UNK] 6a, 6b, -7
3rd Iowa Cavalry. 1-5-14.
3rd Michigan Cavalry. 3-32-13.
3rd Minnesota Volunteers. 2-27-16 (m.); 2-31-27 (m.).
3rd U. S. Infantry. 1-6-5.
13th Army Corps. 4-45-6, 14; 4-46-13, 22, 40; 4-47-4, 30, 31; 5-57-15; 5-59-[35-37]; 5-62-9, 28, 35; 5-64-16. [SEE ALSO: Divisions by number].
13th Illinois Cavalry Volunteers. 2-27-9 (m.).
30th Missouri Volunteer Infantry (Consolidated Organization). 3-36-34.
35th Regiment Wisconsin Infantry Volunteers. 5-64-19, 20.
31st Massachusetts Mounted Infantry. 4-47-46.
34th Indiana Veteran Volunteer Infantry. 5-64-25; 6-71-24.
37th Illinois Infantry. 4-46-11; 6-71-25.
37th Regiment Illinois Veteran Volunteer Infantry. 5-65-13; 5-66-18; 5-67-18, 19, 20; 6-68-9.
36th Iowa Infantry. 2-14-16.
Thomas, Charles. (d. 1878). 3-36-13; 6-75-5 (stamp), 12 (stamp).
Thomas, George Henry (1816-1870). 5-55-4 (copy), 12 (copy).
Thomas, L. 7 vol.)-recipient.
Thompson, Mary. 5-64-14.
Thompson, William (1813-1897). 5-57-16.
Tipton, Mrs. E. _. 5-57-32, 33.
Tompkins, Sam D. 2-21-24.
Totten, James (d. 1871). 3-35-14; 3-39-40, 41; 3-40-24, 25; 3-41-46; 3-42-29, 30, 58, 59; 4-50-25 (tel.); 4-51-12 (tel.), 48, 72 (tel.); 4-53-8 (copy), 57 (tel.), 58 (tel.); 5-57-25; 5-59-40; 6-71-7; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Townsend, Edward Davis (1817-1893). 2-19-19; 2-23-21 (stamp); 3-32-19 (copy); 3-33-28; 3-35-10 (stamp); 3-36-8 (stamp); 3-42-46 (stamp?); 4-45-19 (stamp?); 4-47-48; 4-49-11 (stamp?); 5-61-3 (stamp?), 9 (stamp?); 5-62-28, 42 (stamp?); 5-64-4 (stamp?); 6-68-5 (stamp?); 6-76-5 (stamp); 6-78-2; 6-79-12 (stamp).
Treadwell, Thomas James. 2-30-11, 12 (stamp).
Treasury Department, U. S. 6-80-5.
Trevino, Andres. 5-66-2; 6-69-7; 6-71-23 (m.).
Tripler, A. B. 3-40-23; 4-43-33.
Trull, George G. 5-65-7, 8; 5-67-1.
Tucker, George. 4-47-16.
Tucker, S. H. 2-15-9; 2-28-16b.
Turner, Anne. 2-17-5.
Turner, John Wesley (1833-1899). 6-74-6.
20th Regiment Iowa Volunteer Infantry. 3-37-18; 3-42-60.
28th Regiment Illinois Infantry Veteran Volunteers. 3-40-9; 5-64-26; 6-71-26.
25th Regiment U. S. Colored Infantry. 4-45-15.
21st New York Battery. 3-40-35; 3-42-31.
24th Battalion Indiana Veteran Volunteer Infantry. 5-65-14; 5-66-19, 20; 5-67-21; 6-68-10.
24th Indiana Volunteers. 3-38-3 (m.); 7 (vol.)-recipient.
29th Iowa Infantry. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
29th Regiment Illinois Infantry Veteran Volunteers. 5-66-3 (m.), 4, 21.
26th New York Battery. 3-36-36; 3-42-10; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
33rd Iowa Infantry Volunteers. 3-37-19; 5-62-35.
Union Party-Oregon. 6-73-3.
U. S. Expeditionary Forces [Alabama?]. 5-55-29; 5-57-6, 7.
U. S. Forces, Barrancas, Florida. 4-45-7; 4-46-41, 42; 6-71-27.
U. S. Forces, Blakely, Alabama. 4-52-8, 16.
U. S. Forces East of Mobile Bay. 4-54-14, 22.
U. S. Forces, Expeditionary Steamer Tarascon-Board of Appraisal. 5-55-5.
U. S. Forces Northern Alabama. 5-57-8, 9, 30; 5-58-16, 21, 22; 5-59-15.
U. S. Forces, Kenner, Louisiana. 3-36-41; 3-37-31; 3-38-19, 29, 30, 46, 47; 3-39-42; 3-40-36; 3-41-9, 10; 4-43-11.
U. S. Forces, Kenner, Louisiana-Board of Appraisal. 3-40-37.
U. S. Forces, Kenner, Louisiana-Chief Medical Office. 3-37-47; 3-38-10, 11, 20, 48; 3-39-11, 25, 43, 44; 3-40-10, 26; 3-41-17, 30.
[U. S. Forces, Kenner, Louisiana]-Division of West Mississippi-Reserve Corps- Office Chief Quartermaster. 3-37-4, [14-16], 26, 27; 3-38-15; 3-39-15, 45, 46; 3-40-11; 4-43-9.
U. S. Forces Operating from Pensacola Bay. 4-46-29; 4-48-[7-9]; 4-49-28; 4-50-2; 4-53-59.
U. S. Military Academy. 3-36-2.
U. S. Regiments, etc. SEE 1st, 2nd, etc.
U. S. Sanitary Commission, California Branch of the 1-9-7b (copy).
U. S. Senate Committee on the Conduct of the War. 5-59-18a.
Unknown (unsigned, incomplete signature, illegible or otherwise unidentifiable). 1-8-1 (unsigned); 2-15-33 (James [G.?]; 2-16-6 (illegible); 2-20-21 (Stewart _____ illegible); 2-25-3 (illegible); 2-28-23 (Clara to Dear Sister); 4-48-21 (initial D, official signature illegible); 4-52-17 (unsigned); 5-64-15 (unsigned); 6-71-[28-30] (unsigned); 6-86-18 (initials illegible); 6-87-2a (a Steele? fragment unsigned) (6-87-3b. (Kitty).); 6-88-15 (Maria), 16 (no name), 17 (a&b) (unsigned, illegible report of a battle), 18 (fragment unsigned)
Van Andre, S. G. 3-42-11.
Van Voast, Edward. 4-47-49, 57.
Veatch, James Clifford (1819-1895). 4-49-18; 4-50-8; 7 (vol.)-recipient; 8 (vol.)-recipient.
Veracruz [Mexico] Railroad. 6-68-7 (m.).
Vermont Regiments, etc. SEE 7th Vermont Veteran Volunteers.
Vicksburg, Mississippi. 1-4-6 (map), 12 (map), 13, 14 (map), 17; 1-5-4 (map), 5 (map); 1-8-18.
Victoria, British Columbia, Canada. 6-73-11.
Vincent, Thomas McCurdy. 3-38-31 (copy); 5-63-3.
Voglison [sic], William McKendree (d. 1893). 1-4-9.
Wade, Benjamin Franklin (1800-1878). 5-59-18a.
Wafford, Jeff. S. 4-51-88 (copy).
Wage, E. I. 3-38-22.
Wagenhals, Samuel. 3-38-19.
Wait, William B. 2-15-9.
Walker, W. 1-11-25.
Walling, S. A. 3-35-12
Walther, George H. 5-64-19, 20.
War Department. 5-61-27a.
War Department-Adjutant General's Office. 1-1-2; 1-7-1a, 6, 7; 1-9-4, 10; 1-10-9, 21; 2-15-30; 2-16-2; 2-18-9, 21; 2-19-[3-5], 8, 13, 14, 16, 19, 20; 2-20-3, 8, 17,22, [24-27]; 2-21-15, 17, 21, 25, 26, 33; 2-22-3, 6, 10, 13; 2-23-3, 6, 7, 13, 14, 16, 21, 24, 25; 2-24-8, 11, 15, 22, 23,[26-28]; 2-25-5, 13, 14; 2-26-3, 8, 9, 17, 25; 2-27-2, 3, 7, 8, 11, 20; 2-28-[1-3],10, 11, 15, 28; 2-29-7, 8, 13, 14, 26, 27; 2-30-5, 6, 9, 10; 2-31-14, 15, 26, 28, 29, 31, 32; 3-32-6; 3-33-7, 16,[21-24],[28-30]; 3-34-[5-8], 10, 18, 29; 3-35-5, 6, [8-10], 13, 15, 16, 19, 20; 3-36-8, 22, 23; 3-37-42; 3-38-12, 21, 32, 33, 49; 3-39-25; 3-40-27, 38; 3-42-[19-21],[43-46]; 4-43-12, 13, 22, 39, 40; 4-44-8, 15, 17, 21, 26, 37; 4-45-19; 4-46-[14-16],[43-45], 52; 4-47-[5-7]; 4-48-[10-12], [16-20], 38; 4-49-[9-11], 14,17, 29; 4-51-[27-29],[49-54], 73; 4-52-34; 4-53-[20-22],[30-32], 60; 4-54-15, 23, 28; 5-55-6, 7, 13, 16; 5-57-[10-12], 26, 42; 5-58-[5-7], 10, 11, 17, 18,[23-26], 28, 29; 5-59-1, 2, 4, 6,[7-9], 5-59-13, 23, 25, 26, 29, 30, 38,[41-43]; 5-60-3, [5-9],[12-32]; 5-61-[1-7],[9-16],[18-20], 24, 25, 27b, 32, 33; 5-62-2,[11-13], 23,[26-34], 36, 39, 42, 43; 5-63-1, 3, 5, 11, 13, 14, 20, 27; 5-64-3, 4; 5-65-1, 6; 6-68-5; 6-76-5. [SEE ALSO: Adjutant General's Office, Washington, D. C.; Army, Headquarters of the-Adjutant General's Office].
War Department-Bureau of Refugees, Freedmen and Abandoned Lands. 5-59-3, 14, 18b, 33, 34; 5-60-17; 5-62-16, 17, 20. [SEE ALSO: Bureau of Refugees, Freedmen and Abandoned Lands].
War Department-Ordnance Office. 1-12-3; 2-26-11; 2-30-11, 13; 3-34-40.
War Department, Savannah, Georgia. 3-37-20.
Warner, Camp, Oregon SEE Camp Warner, Oregon.
Warren, William Frederick. 4-46-31, 46, 49, 50; 4-47-8, 17, 18; 4-50-14; 4-51-30a, 30b, 55, 74, 75, 92; 4-52-35.
Washburn, Cadwallader Colder (1818-1882). 1-3-12 (copy).
Waters, James H. 6-85-12.
Webber, Jules C. (d. 1872). 4-54-16.
Weitzel, Godfrey (1835-1884). 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Welch, Deming Norris (d. 1885). 2-23-15.
Wells, Samuel F. 1-13-20.
West, Joseph Rodman (1822-1898). 2-17-9 (m.); [2-23-19 (m.)]; 2-24-1 (m.).
West SEE Department of the West.
West Mississippi SEE Division of West Mississippi.
Western Clarion, The, Helena, Arkansas. 1-13-1.
Western District of Texas. 5-63-23, 28; 5-64-5, 8, 16, 17; 5-65-4; 6-69-6; 7 (vol.)-(m.).
Wheeler, Junius Brutus (d. 1886). 1-10-35; 2-29-24, 30, 32; 2-30-2; 3-33-13, 17; 3-37-48; 4-52-40; 4-54-29.
Wheeler, O. C. 1-9-7b (copy).
Whitcomb, Frank E. 5-64-6.
White, L. C. 3-32-23.
White, Robert [?]. T. 1-9-17; 2-29-34; 3-33-1, 15; 3-35-22, 29.
Whittelsey, Charles Henry (d. 1871). 2-24-8; 5-67-5 (m.); 6-68-2 (m.), 14 (m.); 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Whittier, Charles Albert. 6-80-7 (copy); 6-82-2 (m.).
Wilbur, George L. 3-36-3, 4; 3-40-4,[14-17], 22, 31, 32; 3-41-13,[22-24],[37-39]; 3-42-6, 7, 14, 15, 24, 25,[36-39], 51, 52; 4-43-[4-7], 19, 23, 25, 26, 34; 4-44-25; 4-45-22.
Wilkin, Alexander. 1-1-10; 2-18-10.
Wilkin's Plantation, Alabama. 8 (vol.)-(m.).
Wilkinson, William T. 3-36-34; 3-42-56; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Williams, Charles H. 3-38-29, 20.
Williams, George. 6-72-7, 8; 6-73-5, 6; 6-74-1, 10; 6-75-9; 6-78-3,[6-[11?]]; 6-79-1, 2, 5, 14, 15; 6-80-1, 3, 4, 9, 10; 6-81-1, 6; 6-82-1, 4, 6, 10; 6-83-[1-3], 7; 6-85-1, 5, 7, 9; 6-86-1, 2, 7, 9, 11, 12, 13.
Williams, James Monroe. 2-14-6.
Williams, John A. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Williams, [Robert] (d. 1901). 6-71-4.
Willson, Charles H. 1-9-26.
Wilshire, W. W. 1-8-10.
Wilson, James 6-87-4.
Wilson, James Harrison (1837-1925). 2-30-20 (m.); 5-57-17 (copy).
Wilson, John Moulder. 3-41-46; 4-45-13; 5-51-93; 5-57-43; 5-64-18.
Wilson's Creek, Missouri, Battle of 1-1-13, 15; 5-63-10. box 9 folder 9
Wimmer, William P. 4-52-5, 41; 8 (vol.)-recipient.
Winnemucca (Piute Indian). 6-73-8 (m.).
Wisconsin Regiments, etc. SEE 35th Regiment Wisconsin Infantry Volunteers.
Wiswell, E. M. 3-37-35, 36.
Wolford, Herman. 5-55-5; 6-71-25.
Wood, A. P. 6-70-1b.
Wood, A[mji?]. 5-63-6.
Wood, Ed T. 2-16-5.
Wood, Oliver. 2-31-33.
Woodman, E. W. 4-46-28; 4-47-51.
Woodruff, Fanny C. 1-11-7.
Woodruff, Mrs. Jane E. 1-11-11.
Woodruff, Mary C. 1-11-7.
Woods, Charles Robert (1827-1885). 1-5-13.
Woodward, Samuel Lippincott. 5-55-10, 12, 25; 5-57-17.
Woolfolk, George-Trial of. 2-30-6.
Worth, (Miss) M. S. 1-8-4.
Wright, Horatio Gouverneur (1820-1899). 5-63-12a; 5-66-10; 6-68-14; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Wurtemberg, _____ (Vice-Consul of France, Matamoros, Mexico). 5-67-14.
Wuerpel, Ernest. 6-88-13a (printed).
Yarrington, George E. 4-47-32.
Yazoo, Mississippi. 1-5-6 (map).
Yeakle, M. M. 1-11-10.
Yeatman, Th. H. 1-8-9, 13, 15.
[Yoreley?], T. D. W. 3-33-1.
Zulavsky, L. L. 5-59-10.
Abbreviations and Symbols
ADf Autograph draft
ADS Autograph document signed
A.G.O. Adjutant General's Office
ALS Autograph letter signed
ANS Autograph note signed
Art. Artillery
AWOL Absent without leave
Clip. Clipping
Df Draft
DS Document signed
FS Frederick Steele
Ft Fort
G.C.M.O. General Court Martial Order
G.F.O. General Field Order
G.O. General Order
HQ Headquarters
LS Letter signed
MDWM Military Division of West Mississippi
ms. Manuscript
N North
n.d. No date
No. Number
n.p. No place
NS Note signed
POW Prisoner of war
s. Signed
S.F.O. Special Field Order
S.O. Special Order
Sra. Sonora
Tel. Telegram
[] Information supplied
[?] Information questionable 1-1-1 equals Box 1, folder1, item 1.